Avatar: The Deep Dive - A Special Edition of 20/20 is a
documentary film directed by Dave Hoffman.
An inside look at one of the most anticipated movie
sequels ever with James Cameron and cast.
Self, played by Chris Connelly.
Self, played by James Cameron.
Self, played by Zoe Saldaña.
Self, played by Sigourney Weaver.
Self, played by Kate Winslet.
Self, played by Stephen Lang.
The Abyss is a 1989 American science fiction film written and directed by James Cameron
and starring Ed Harris, Mary Elizabeth Mastrantonio, and Michael Biehn.
When an American submarine sinks in the Caribbean, a U.S.
search and recovery team works with an oil platform crew,
racing against Soviet vessels to recover the boat.
Deep in the ocean, they encounter something unexpected.
The film was released on August 9, 1989 by 20th Century Fox, receiving
generally positive reviews and grossed $90 million.
At the 62nd Academy Awards, it was nominated for four
Academy Awards, winning Best Visual Effects.